Jeremy Books

3D Modeller and Lighting Artist

3333 Commercial Dr. Vancouver, BC

Phone: 778-227-2868

Email: <u>jeremy.books@gmail.com</u>
Website: www.jeremybooks.com

Skillset: 3D modeling, texturing, lighting and shading

Recently I graduated from Vancouver Film School's 3D Animation and Visual Effects program, gaining a strong passion as a 3D modeller and lighting artist. Shortly after, I joined the game industry as a Quality Assurance tester, I am very excited and determined to start working as an artist within this industry.

Education:

Diploma – 3D Animation and Visual Effects

April 2013- April 2014

Vancouver Film School – 3D Animation and Visual Effects

Work Experience:

Computer Technician

ContinuIT - Goderich, Ontario

January 2012 - July 2012

Co-op position, built, cleaned and hardware troubleshoot desktop computers and laptops

Quality Assurance

Electronic Arts – Burnaby British Columbia

July 2014 - Present

Temporary full time

Technical proficiencies:

Maya, Mudbox, Zbrush, Photoshop, Nuke, Renderman

References:

Craig Shiells – Lighting InstructorVancouver Film SchoolEmail: cshiells@telus.netColin Gilles – Animation InstructorVancouver Film SchoolEmail: cgiles@vfs.comTravis Guthrie - Modelling InstructorVancouver Film SchoolEmail: tguthrie@vfs.com